Siddharth Milind Konduru

6 Candeltree Dr. # 3 • Springfield, IL 62704 **CELL PHONE** [217-761-6199] • skond7@uis.edu

OBJECTIVE

Technical associate that will use prior experience in IT related profession.

SUMMARY

B.A in Electronic and Communication and with 1 year experience at Amazon.com, Inc. as a business process analyst. Currently an MIS graduate student, flexible problem solver with excellent attention to detail. Can easily assimilate in both individual and team work settings.

EDUCATION

University of Illinois, Springfield, IL

Master of Science in Management Information Systems

Institute of Aeronautical Engineering, Hyderabad, Andhra Pradesh

Bachelor of Electronic and Communication Engineering

Expected: May 2016

TECHNICAL SKILLS

- Hands on knowledge with Microsoft exchange server and Linux operating systems and Exchange.
- Graduate with solid academic skills and considerable experience planning and implementing programs, projects, and public-relations events.
- CCNA (Cisco Certified Network Associate) trained
- Well versed in .Net, C, C++ and ASP .Net

WORK EXPERIENCE / INTERNSHIP

University of Illinois, Springfield, Springfield, IL

Graduate Student Hourly

- Manage upgrades of department web page.
- Research, design and lead program offerings.
- Organize people and initiatives.
- Conduct special events and trainings.
- Photograph and design program graphics and media

Amazon.com,Inc Hyderabad, Andhra Pradesh

June 2013 - June 2014

July 2015 - May 2016

Business Process Developer/Customer Service Associate

- Communicated with Aces team in KAI-ZEN projects to improve and streamline business processes at Amazon.
- Responsible for assessing employers performance and provide feedback.
- Responded to customers' e-mails and answered queries regarding the orders placed.

Mag Web Technologies Hyderabad, Andhra Pradesh

September 2012 - April 2013

Project Trainee

- Worked with ASP.Net and C# back end SQL Server in MAG Web Technologies as a project trainee.
- Developed a program using ASP.Net and C# programming with back end as SQL Server as part of RMI (CMS) Project.

SCHOOL ACTIVITIES / INTERESTS

- Founder and President of TARA meditation club
- Chief graphic designer of Asian Student Organization (ASO)
- Co-Chair of UIS It's On US, White House Bystander Intervention Campaign.

May 2012